So we created the action creator,
Bylece gerek yaratcy yarattk.
let's now connect it to our contact data container.
imdi iletiim verileri konteynerize balanalm.
There we have the orderHandler method
Orada ileyici yntemini sipari etmeliyiz.
and I will leave it here because I still need it,
Ve onu burada brakacam, nk yine de ihtiyacm var.
it should be executed when we clicked the order button. But I no longer want to handle loading here so
Sipari dmesini tkladmzda yrtlmelidir ancak buradan yklemeyi artk istemiyorum,
I will remove setState loading there and I no longer want to actually do the order here,
bylece ykleme ileminin kald yerden kaldrlacak ve artk burada sipari vermek istemiyorum.
I already stripped out the code to reach out to axios. What I do want to do,
Yapmak istediim bilgiye erimek iin kodu elden karmaya balamtm.
I want to leave the axios
Eriimden ayrlmak istiyorum.
imput here, import here
thalatnz buraya yaptrn.
and I actually didn't do something else before,
Aslnda daha nce baka bir ey yapmadm.
I want to import withErrorHandler, that higher order component from my higher order component folder,
Yksek sipari bileeni klasrmdeki yksek sipari bileeni hata ileyicisi ile almak istiyorum.
I don't need to do that it's not related to redux but I want to make sure that I do use it here
Redux'la ilgisi olmadn, ancak burada kullanacamdan emin olmak istiyorum.
too just as I use it in the burger builder at the bottom, it's getting wrapped by the connect middleware
Q Sanayiyi alt kattaki Bergere kayalarnda kullandm gibi katman yazlmn balamak iin sarlyorum
and I want to have this error dropdown here too.
ve bu hatann da buraya dmesini istiyorum.
So in contact data at the very bottom where I export everything, I'll wrap contact data with one additional
da aktarmak iin, bir baka yksek sipari bileeni ile tm sarg iletiim verisi hata ileyicisine sahip yksek sipari
higher order component, my withErrorHandler higher order component where I don't only pass contact data
bileeni yazm yalnzca iletiim verilerini deil ayn zamanda kk bir ey olan eriimi de iletir.
but also axios, that's just a tiny thing.
Yani ok altndaki iletiim verilerinde, her eyi
The main thing is that I want to connect my container here to the new actions I created and for that,
nemli olan, konteyneri burada oluturduum yeni eylemlerime balamak iin bir kez ekleyin ve bu
I need to connect myself to the dispatchable actions,
nedenle eylemlerin gnderilmesine kendimi balamam gerekiyor.
so I'll add a constant mapDispatchToProps, we didn't have that before
Bu yzden daha nce sahip olmadmz sabit bir harita gnderimi ekleyeceim.
and here, I now have one property I want to create, onOrderBurger or any name you like. There,
Ve burada sipari burgeri veya orada holandnz herhangi bir ad zerinde yaratmak istediim bir mlk var.
I'll execute an anonymous function where I in the end dispatch my action creator, the action creator
Gerekten eylem yaratanm eylem yaratcs gnderdiim anonim bir ilev yrtrm.
I added in the order file, purchaseBurgerStart.
Satn alma sonbaharnda Burger balangcnda dzenleme yapyorum.
That is the action creator
Gerek yaratc budur.
I want to import in my index.js file in the actions folder so that I can reach it from other files
Dizinime Chia'nn eylemler klasrnde dmesini bylece dier dosyalardan alabilmelerini ve Arafa'y
and that other file I want to reach it from is the contact data container,
iletiim verileri kapsaycsndan okumak istedim.
there, I'll now import it. So I'll import everything as actions from
imdi ithal edildi, bu nedenle her eyi, eylemler gibi ie aktarn.
and now I'll move all the way up to store actions there
Ve imdi hepsi orada eylemleri depolamak iin hareket ediyor.
in the index.js file.
ndeks j aadaki gibidir.
And with that, I can dispatch at the bottom of the contact data container,
Ve bununla konteynrn altndaki konteynerde sevk edebilirim.
I can dispatch actions and then here, it's purchaseBurgerStart. Now I do expect to get an argument
Harekat gnderebilirim ve burada burada satn alma hrszlar balyor, burada bir tartma beklemeyi
here,
umuyorum.
the order data,
Sipari verileri.
so I get it into my anonymous function and I pass it on to that action creator because I do actually
Bu yzden onu anonim bir ileve alyorum ve onu eylem yaratcya gnderiyorum.
expect that data here in the action creator. Now in contact data,
nk burada eylem oluturulan verilerin imdi temas verilerinde olmasn bekliyorum.
I of course also want to use this property.
Elbette bu mlk kullanmak istiyorum.
So onOrderBurger should be called in the orderBurgerHandler,
Bu yzden sipari bir burger sipari burger ileyici olarak arlmaldr.
let's scroll up to the orderHandler and there, we prepare the order data,
Sipari ileyicisine gidelim ve sipari verilerini hazrlyoruz.
now we can execute this.props,
imdi bu sahne idamn yapabiliriz.
remember we always receive our dispatch actions here as props, onOrderBurger
Unutmayn, gnderim eylemlerimizi sipari burgeri sahas olarak alyoruz.
and there I want to pass my order
Ve emrimi gemek istiyorum.
and this contains the ingredients, the price and here, order data is simply the detailed order data the user entered
Ve bu, srpriz maddeleri ieriyor ve sipari verileriniz, kullancnn forma girdii ayrntlar
into the form.
veya verilerden oluuyor.
With that, we are able to dispatch this on a click but there are a couple of things which won't work as
Bununla birlikte, bir tklamayla gnderilebiliyoruz, ancak artk beklenen ekilde almayacak birka
expected anymore.
ey var.
For example, in the render method of the contact data component here, we check if we are loading to eventually
rnein, render ynteminde tm iletiim verileri bileeni burada, sonuta Espen'i grntlemek iin yklenip yklenmediimizi kontrol
display a spinner if we are instead of the form.
eder veya formun yerine geeriz.
Now we are loading
imdi yklyoruz.
if we clicked the order button. We need to handle that loading state in our redux store
Sipari dmesini tklarsa, redock deponuzda bu ykleme durumunu ele almamz gerekir.
therefore, because we put the whole process of ordering into redux. To be able to do, so we need to work
Bu nedenle, yapabilmek iin redoksa tm sipari verme srecini koyduk, u an olduka bo olan
on the reducer which is pretty empty right now.
redktr zerinde almamz gerekiyor.
So that's the next goal,
te bu bir sonraki hedef.
let's work on that order reducer.
Sipari indirgeciyle alalm.